[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Hancock is the first movie in which Will Smith plays a superhero.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1967 film starred Dustin Hoffman who asked the question: Mrs. Robinson, youre trying to seduce me. Arent you?.", "correct_answer": "The Graduate", "incorrect_answers": ["John and Mary", "All the Presidents Men", "Kramer vs. Kramer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about squirrels?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Some squirrel species are omnivorous.", "Most squirrels are active in the daytime.", "They cannot digest cellulose."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What animals raised Tarzan, one of the greatest movie heroes according to the American Film Institute?", "correct_answer": "Apes", "incorrect_answers": ["Tigers", "Wolves", "Panthers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played Captain Lansen in the 1968 movie The Lost Continent?", "correct_answer": "Eric Porter", "incorrect_answers": ["Ben Carruthers", "Norman Eshley", "James Cossins"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the beginning of the movie Back to the Future, while riding on his skateboard, Marty grabs hold of which vehicle first?", "correct_answer": "pick-up truck", "incorrect_answers": ["taxi cab", "jeep wrangler", "police car"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He played Doc Gaylen Adam on the television program Gunsmoke.", "correct_answer": "Milburn Stone", "incorrect_answers": ["Ken Curtis", "Will Geer", "Dennis Weaver"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1776, 400 British and Hessian troops land in The Bronx.  A group of 400 American troops held them off while Washington got the main army away safely.  What was this battle called ?", "correct_answer": "The Battle of Pells Point", "incorrect_answers": ["The Battle of Throgs Neck", "The Battle of Eastchester", "The Battle of The Bronx"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these was invented by O. Mumford Scott?", "correct_answer": "Inexpensive weed-free grass seed", "incorrect_answers": ["Disposable razors", "The electric car", "Vaseline"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What term refers to the events following the climax in a dramatic play?", "correct_answer": "Denouement", "incorrect_answers": ["Denorment", "Delouges", "Delarges"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There is hardly any one who has not heard the fairy-tale of Snow White. Who was it written by?", "correct_answer": "Brothers Grimm", "incorrect_answers": ["Gianni Rodari", "Charles Perrault", "Hans Christian Andersen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How was the South Asian bread called Puri prepared?", "correct_answer": "By frying", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "By baking", "By boiling"]}]